29.0%		27 	Correct
 7.5%		 7 	Input not in bigrams
 2.2%		 2 	Output not in bigrams
10.8%		10 	Failed Stem
 3.2%		 3 	Failed Build
45.2%		42	Word not chosen
 2.2%		 2 	Wrong word chosen, but is grammatically correct
 0.0%		 0 	Wrong word chosen, not grammatically correct
 0.0%		 0 	Input errors
————————————————————————
100.1%		93	Total

+++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++

29.0%		27	Correct
54.8%		51	Limited by corpus
 2.2%		 2 	Wrong word chosen, but is grammatically correct
 0.0%		 0 	Wrong word chosen, not grammatically correct
14.0%		13	Morphological Errors
 0.0%		 0	User Input Errors
————————————————————————
100.0%		93	Total